Michael Gullo

Developer / Programmer

I've been programming for 15+ years and am a recent graduate from the Case Western Reserve University Full Stack program (having been a consistent A+ student)... solidifying my skills as a developer/programmer and am now ready to pursue programming as a career.

Not only do I take pride in my coding efficiency and proficiency, I'm always eager to expand my skills into new areas. Solving problems, understanding the code and becoming better at programming has become very addictive.

WORK EXPERIENCE

T2M2, Concord Twsp, Oh — Computer Server Design / Maintenance

April 2016 - PRESENT

Designed, built, programmed and maintain 279 cryptocurrency mining servers.

Automatic Music, Concord Twsp, Oh— Electronics Technician

September 1982- December 2018

Troubleshooting of mechanical and electrical systems, including component level circuit board repair.

Extensive experience with technical equipment; including volt meters, ammeters, oscilloscopes, etc.

Designed and implemented many aftermarket modifications and upgrades of both electronic and mechanical systems.

EDUCATION

Case Western Reserve University, Cleveland, Oh — Certification

January 2019 - July 2019 Full Stack Program

Lakeland Community College, Kirtland, Ohio

April 1984 - November 1985 Electronics Technology

PERSONAL INFO

Address

2645 Hickory Lane Pepper Pike, OH 44124

Phone

(440) 476-7956

Email

mikegullo4747@gmail.com

GitHub

https://github.com/mike14747

Portfolio

https://mike14747.github.io/

SKILLS

Javascript / JQuery

MySQL / MongoDB / Sequelize ORM

Node JS / Express Server

React JS

MVC Framework

HTML5 / CSS3 (including Bootstrap and Handlebars)

PHP

Mobile-first, responsive designs